从现在开始，算我一个
From now on, count on me.
- 日尔诺夫? - 一切都是从那里开始的
- Zhrnov? - It all started from there.
他被复活的人杀死了
He was killed by the one who returned.
- 谁? ! - 吸血鬼！
- Who?! - A vampire!
我认为凶手在传递一些信息
I think the killer is sending some messages.
你是说，惩罚他们？
You mean, like, punishing them?
法官和维多杰都是日尔诺夫纪念碑委员会的成员
The judge and Vidoje were members of the board for the demolition of Zhrnov.
还有另外一件事把他们联系在一起
There's another thing that connects them...
赌博
Gambling.
我听说他们吵起来了
I've heard he was yelling.
说了一些难听的话
There were some hard words.
严重的威胁
Serious threats.
我们需要赌场的地址
We need the address of the casino.
不能告诉你
Can't tell you that.
他欠我一大笔钱
He owed me a huge amount of money.
让我卷入了一桩肮脏的生意，我还害了我儿子
And got me into a dirty business. I screwed my son over, too.
所以迪米特里耶维奇在收集反对拆迁的签名
So Dimitriyevich was collecting signatures against the demolition.
事实上，他们签的就是
And in fact, those signatures were an agreement
同意拆除贫民窟的协议
to demolish the Yataghan slum.
我什么时候能拿到钱？
When will I get paid?
文件经法庭核实后
After the document is certified in court.
一个叫托马斯维奇的人出现了，他和马其顿人合作
Some Tomasovich appeared. He works with Macedonians.
他还和贫民窟的人有来往
He also connected with those from Yataghan slum.
这是海洛因，我们的新工作
This is heroin. Our new job.
阿尔索夫回来了
Hadzi Arsov is back.
你要把那个疯子带到这里来
You'll bring me that lunatic here.
共产国际突然对我们的组织产生了兴趣
The Comintern suddenly began to take an interest in our organization.
因为暗杀国王的计划已经开始了
Because the assassination of the king is being planned.
如果这世上有忠诚
If there is loyalty,
这个女人就是忠诚的化身
then it is in this woman.
- 你从来没有骗过我? - 没有
- And you would never lie to me? - Never.
你为什么把那些照片给萨夫科维奇？
Why did you give those photos to Savkovich?
你真该看看他的表情
You should've seen his face.
萨夫科维奇必须消失
Savkovich must disappear.
维多杰与萨洛尼卡审判有关吗？
Has Vidoje had anything to do with the Thessaloniki process?
我认为有关
I think he has.
一切都围绕着它
Everything revolves around that.
我们去贫民窟
We'll hit the Yataghan slum.
“今晚10点来找我这很重要——维多杰”
"Come to me tonight at 10. It's important. Vidoje"
他们都是由一个人联系在一起的
They're all connected by one man.
迪米特里耶维奇会给我们解释清楚
Dimitriyevich will have to explain some things to us.
兄弟姐妹们！
Brothers and sisters!
我的亚塔汗同胞们！
My Yataghanians!
他们想要让亚塔汗贫民窟
They want to wipe this poor Yataghan slum of ours
从地球上消失！
off the face of the earth!
那些靠我们的不幸发财的人！
Those who got rich on our misfortune!
那些因为我们流血而得到好处的人..
Those who got paid very well for our blood...
我们的眼泪..
Our tears...
还有我们死去的同胞！
And our dead people!
不应该是这样的！
It can't be that way!
如果亚塔汗贫民窟被烧毁
If the Yataghan slum is burned,
整个贝尔格莱德也将付之一炬！
the whole Belgrade will be burned, too!
我向你们保证...
I give you my word...
不杀了阿里姆皮耶 · 米里奇和他所有的走狗
I won't calm down
我誓不罢休
until I kill Alimpiye Mirich and all of his shit!
他们是畜生！
They are shit!
我要弄死他们所有人！
I'm gonna fuck 'em all!
奇妙的幻觉世界
MAGIC LILLY WONDERFUL WORLD OF ILLUSION
巴尔干半岛的阴影 第二季 第六集
BLACK SUN SEASON 2 EPISODE 06
新时代最新一期！
The latest issue of the New Age!
- 你去哪了，督察? ! - 怎么了，日沃因？
- Where are you, Inspector?! - What's wrong, Zhivoyin?
警长在等你
The chief is waiting for you.
- 还有一个目击者! - 谁？
- There's also a witness! - Which one?
就那个! 快点，泽切维奇已经在那儿了
Well, that one! Come on, Zechevich is already there.
- 我们说到哪儿了? - 留言
- Where were we? - The message.
- 维多杰给你的？ - 哦，对了! 留言
- From Vidoje. - Oh, yes! The message.
我必须说，我很惊讶
I was surprised, I must say.
我承认，维多杰先生和我..
I'll admit, Mr. Vidoje and I...
我们不是什么好朋友，我们根本不是朋友
We're not such good friends. We're not friends at all.
“我的朋友，九点在我们的咖啡馆等我”
"My friend, wait for me at nine, in our cafe."
“很紧急，维多杰”
"It's urgent. Vidoje"
他为什么叫我”朋友”?”？
Why the hell did he call me his "friend"?
我们两个是纪念碑建设委员会
The two of us know each other
认识的
from the monument construction committee.
- 还有赌局 - 什么赌局？
- And from card games. - What card games?
非法赌局
Illegal card games.
是啊，你能想象吗? 非法赌局
Yeah, can you imagine? Illegal card games.
咖啡馆和赌局有什么联系？
What has the cafe got to do with playing cards?
我们通常在那里集合，然后去打牌
We'd usually gather there, and then go to a card game.
那天晚上你打牌了吗？
Did you play cards that night?
没有
No.
太奇怪了
That was weird.
我完全不明白他为什么邀请我去那儿
I don't understand at all why he invited me there.
告诉我..
Tell me...
你到底看到了什么？
What exactly did you see?
我可以看到他的公寓，就在街对面
I could see his apartment across the street.
哦，是的! 那也很奇怪
Oh, yes! That was weird, too.
什么? 什么很奇怪？
What? What was weird?
你能给我一支烟吗？
Would you be so kind to offer me a cigarette?
维多杰的公寓
Vidoje's apartment...
你说有些奇怪
You said something was weird.
是啊，很奇怪... 灯都关着
Yeah, it's weird... The lights were off,
一个人从门里出来
a person came out through the gate,
关上大门..
closed the gate...
天很黑，我看不清那是谁
It was dark, I couldn't see who that was.
然后，那个人走进一盏路灯的光里
Then, that person enters into the light of a street lamp,
我才看清他
and I could tell who it was.
你能描述一下那个人吗？
Could you describe that person?
不需要描述，我认识那个人
No need to describe, I know that person.
那是谁？
And who was that?
组织赌局的绅士
The gentleman who organizes card games.
迪米特里耶维奇
Dimitriyevich.
我不相信
I don't believe that.
他看见了
He saw him.
他错了，这不可能
Well, he was wrong. It's impossible.
你知道他没错
You know he wasn't wrong.
他来玩牌多少次了？
How many times did he come to play cards?
很多次
Enough.
你得帮帮我们
You have to help us.
- 我? ! - 是你让我算你一个的
- Me?! - You told me to count on you.
你能不能和他约个时间
If you could possibly make an appointment with him.
你是说给他设套？
You mean, to set him up?
不，为了帮我们抓到凶手
No, but to help us catch the killer.
带我们去他们打牌的地方
And show us the place where they play cards.
我不能带你去因为我答应过..
I can't show you the place because I promised...
你有没有意识到你可能藏匿了凶手？
Are you aware that you may be hiding the killer?
拜托，迪米特里耶维奇就是凶手? ！
Oh, come on! Dimitriyevich is the killer?!
他不会杀任何人
He can't kill anyone.
尤其是索尼娅
Especially not Sonya.
好吧，也许不是他，但他可能参与了什么事
Okay, maybe it wasn't him, but he might be part of something.
天知道谁是幕后黑手！
God knows who's behind this!
让我们和他谈谈
Just let us talk to him.
我知道你们是朋友但是..
I know you're friends but...
不要被那种亲密所欺骗
Don't be deceived by that closeness.
是的
Yeah.
它具有危险的欺骗性
It can be dangerously deceiving.
好吧
Okay.
你要我怎么做？
What do you want me to do?
哦，天哪，他们真的把这个地方烧了！
Oh, boy, they really burned this!
你很抱歉..
And you're so sorry...
我只是说说
I'm just saying.
没烧你家就行，不是吗？
It's easy when it's not about your ass, is it?
- 爸爸! - 怎么了？
- Dad! - What?
我该怎么处理这块烧过的木头？
What should I do with this burnt wood?
滚犊子！
Stick it up your ass!
这算什么问题? ！
What kind of question is that?!
- 他妈的! - 别说废话了
- Oh, for fuck's sake! - Stop that bullshit.
- 是他派你来的? - 是的
- Did he send you? - Yes.
- 你叫什么? - 马诺伊洛
- What's your name? - Manoylo.
革命者，过来！
Revolutionary, come here!
你的人来找你了
Your people came for you.
他不是我的人
They're not mine.
对不起，我忘了你有自己的战争
Sorry, I forgot you have your own war.
好吧，让我告诉你我是怎么打仗的
All right, let me show you how I run my war.
大家都知道我们需要钱和武器
Guys, you know the deal, we need money and weapons.
要有武器，我们需要钱
To have weapons, we need money.
为了有钱，我们需要卖东西
To have money, we need to sell goods.
是的，老板！
Yes, boss!
达米安！
Damyan!
来吧，马诺伊洛！
Come on, Manoylo!
随着年龄的增长，我越来越想念父亲
The older I get, the more I feel like I miss my father.
别误会
Don't get me wrong.
你总是在我身边
You were always there for me.
但我想知道..
But I would like to know...
他是个什么样的人
what kind of man he was.
你让我想起了他
You remind me of him.
他不是一个随和的人
He wasn't an easy man.
但他的行为总是正确的
But he always acted correctly.
如果我也能做到的话
If I could at least do that.
我相信他会为你感到骄傲的
I'm sure he would be proud of you.
你告诉我他真的相信..
You told me that he really believed...
图勒组织可以让世界变得更美好
The Thules could make the world a better place for everyone.
但我们今天变成了什么
And what have we become today...
在我看来，我们只是在帮助这个世界
It seems to me that we're only helping the world
更快毁灭
go to hell even faster.
发生了很多可怕的事情
Terrible things are being prepared.
我不想成为其中的一员
I don't want to be a part of it.
事实上，我希望我能阻止他们
In fact, I wish I could stop them.
但恐怕不行
But I'm afraid I can't.
亲爱的，人到了我这个年纪
My dear, when a man reaches my age,
就会知道什么是生命中最重要的
he knows to determine what's most important in his life.
对我来说，你就是最重要的
To me, it's you.
你必须辞职
You have to prepare a resignation.
离开这里，越快越好
You have to disappear. As soon as possible.
丹尼卡同志，你想我了吗？
Comrade Danica, did you miss me?
你迟到了
You're late.
你想我了
So, you missed me.
但这不是我的错
But it's not my fault.
我们的同志习惯了舒适的坐骑
Our colleague is used to comfortable rides,
所以我们并不着急
so we weren't in a hurry.
没关系，交给我吧
It's okay, leave it to me.
乐意之至
With pleasure.
下午好，哈吉 · 阿尔索夫同志
Good afternoon, Comrade Hadzi Arsov.
我是丹妮卡，很高兴见到你
My name is Danica, nice to meet you.
我们把话说清楚，我们不是同志，小姐
Let's get this straight. We're not comrades, Miss.
这些是你的文件
These are your documents.
跟我来
Come with me.
你的名字叫瓦尔丹 · 斯托扬诺夫斯基，来自比托拉
Your name will be Vardan Stoyanovski, from Bitola.
如果有人问你的话
If anyone asks you.
但是尽量少说话
But try to talk as little as possible.
你是来保养天文台的
You are here to maintain the observatory and the park.
如果你有什么需要尽管开口
If you need anything, ask me. Just me.
- 清楚了吗? - 是的
- Is that clear? - Yes.
再清楚不过了
It couldn't be any clearer.
我要在这儿呆多久？
How long will I stay here?
这不是我能决定的
It's not up to me.
跟我来
Come with me.
我带你去休息的地方
I'll show you where you sleep.
- 是谁? ! - 是我，塔尼
- Who is it?! - It's me. Tane.
你来干什么？
What do you want?
你怎么不通通风呢？
Why don't you let some fresh air in here?
你的刺刀呢？
Where's your bayonet?
消失了
Disappeared.
- 消失了? - 是的
- Disappeared? - Yes.
你又开始喝酒了？
You're drinking again?
维多杰被杀那晚你在他家做了什么？
What did you do at Vidoje's place the night he was killed?
有人看见你从楼里出来了
They saw you coming out of the building.
有人给我一张纸条，上面写着要我去那里
Someone sent me a note with a message to go there.
我到的时候...
When I arrived...
我发现他们两个都死了
I found them lying dead, both of them.
还有老鼠
And the rat.
为什么维多杰邀请你去他家？
Why would Vidoje invite you over?
迪米特里耶维奇，如果你知道什么
Dimitriyevich, if you know something,
你得告诉我
you have to tell me.
索尼娅被杀了
Sonya was killed.
如果我知道，我会告诉你的，相信我，我发誓我不知道
If I knew, I'd tell you, trust me. I swear I don't know.
我只为他做过一件事
I did one job for him,
我以为他是叫我过去拿钱
I thought he was inviting me to pay me.
我在为我儿子筹学费
I'm raising money for my son's tuition.
我想送他去布达佩斯
I want to send him to Budapest.
你和维多杰有什么过节？
What did you mess with Vidoje, huh?
法官也参与了吗？
Was the judge involved in that, too?
- 重要吗? - 不重要吗? ！
- What does it matter? - What does it matter?!
那个人在你家门口被杀了！
The man was found murdered in front of your door!
那晚你在哪儿？他才会被杀? ！
And where were you that night so he wouldn't be killed?!
你来上班了吗！
Did you come to work?!
- 我不能来 - 你不能来
- I couldn't come. - You couldn't.
答得好
Great answer.
作为朋友，我想问你一件事
Let me ask you something, as a friend.
你对这一切了解多少？
What do you know about all this?
怎么回事？
What's going on?
我不知道
I don't know.
我不知道怎么回事
I don't know what's going on.
每一起谋杀都传递着一个信息
Every murder sends a message.
所有的事情看起来都是有联系的，然而事实并非如此
Everything seems connected, and then again it isn't.
不管怎样，你的名字总是被提到
Anyway, your name is mentioned all the time.
他们在打听你
They're asking about you.
你知道这意味着什么
You know what that means.
好吧
Okay.
如果你不告诉我
If you won't tell me,
去警局把你知道的一切都告诉他们
go to Glavnjacha and tell them everything you know.
你去找他们总比他们来找你好
It's better you go to them than them coming for you.
你知道是怎么回事
But no need to tell you that, you know how it goes.
不管发生什么...
Whatever happens...
你都可以指望我的帮助
You can count on my help.
谢谢你
Thank you.
意大利与南斯拉夫王国边界 波尔托罗兹
PORTOROZ, ITALY BORDER WITH THE KINGDOM OF YUGOSLAVIA
我希望生意进展顺利
I hope the business is progressing.
在你们的帮助下，非常顺利
It is progressing, with your help.
只要你不再把事情弄得更糟...
Only if you could stop making them worse, too...
如果我可以问的话，我怎么让变得更糟了
How am I making them worse? If I may ask.
你叫我来一个大家都认识我的地方
You made an appointment at a hotel where everyone knows me.
有人会看到我的，我下次不来了
Someone will see me. I won't come next time.
别担心露台上的人
Don't worry about these people on the terrace.
所有人的都检查过了
All of them are checked.
都是我们的人
They're working for us.
那你找我来干什么？
Then why do you need me?
只有你能告诉我是谁杀了诺维奇伯爵
Only you can tell me who killed Count Nowicki.
我不能，我的人也不知道
I can't. My people don't know that either.
如果他们知道，早就抓住他了
And if they knew, they would have nailed him
因为诺维奇和我们的人也有联系
because Nowicki was in some connection with our people.
和你的人？
With your people?
诺维奇和你们的人到底有什么关系？
What exactly was Nowicki's connection with your people?
我也不太清楚
I don't know exactly.
我只知道他应该带一些资料文件
All I know is that he should have taken some information paper
但被别人拿走了
but someone else took it instead,
现在我的人民有麻烦了
and now my people are in trouble.
他们不得不改变计划
They have to change the plan.
为什么？
For what?
是关于你的国王
It's about your king.
我们的国王，安特，那也是你的国王！
Our king, Ante, that's your king, too!
你接着说
I'm listening.
正在准备一项新的行动，有关贝尔格莱德
A new action is being prepared. Belgrade is mentioned.
暗杀行动将在贝尔格莱德进行？
The assassination will be in Belgrade?
局长也是这么说的
That's what the chief said.
但我也不认为他什么都知道
But I don't think he knows everything either.
在这之后，大家都沉默了一会儿
After this with Nowicki, everyone fell silent for a while.
贝尔格莱德
Belgrade.
一旦他发现，我也会发现的
As soon as he finds out, I'll find out, too.
有消息立刻告诉我，安特
Let me know now, Ante.
否则，我们的这次交流不会有好结果
Otherwise, this communication of ours won't end well.
新时代
NEW AGE
怎么了，迪米特里耶维奇？
What's wrong, Dimitriyevich?
很重要的事
It's important.
有人看到我在维多杰被杀的那晚从他家出来
They saw me coming out of Vidoje's house the night he was killed.
我去那里是因为他邀请了我
And I was there because he invited me.
他们会指控我杀了他
They'll accuse me of killing him.
是吗？
Well, did you?
- 别开玩笑了 - 谁说我开玩笑了？
- No kidding, please. - Who says I'm kidding?
警察紧跟在你后面你却跑来这里
The police are at your heels and you came here,
他们也会盯上我的
so they'll be at my heels, too.
是这样吗，我亲爱的迪米特里耶维奇？
Is that right, my dear and honest Dimitriyevich?
我们是一条船上的
We're in this together.
真的吗？
Oh, really?
- 我谁也没杀 - 我也是
- I didn't kill anyone. - Me neither.
是你把我扯进来的
You got me involved in this.
如果他们审问我
If they interrogate me,
就一定会来找你的
they'll come to you.
好吧
Well, well...
"当人被逼上绝境，他什么都会说"
"When a man is in trouble, he remembers everything."
你现在想要什么？
And what do you want now?
我要你给我找个地方躲起来
I want you to find me shelter.
我要你找出是谁策划了这一切
I want you to find out who's setting this up.
陷害我的人也会陷害你
The one who set me up, will set you up, too.
听着...
Listen...
除了你自己的人之外，没人知道你的赌场位置
No one knows about your casino except your people.
如果他们不会说，那你最好在赌场躲着
If they are silent, it's best for you to go there and wait.
我会派人去带你走
Someone will come to take you further.
对你来说最明智的就是马上过去
And the smartest thing for you would be to do it right away.
你应该知道你不能再回家了
You realize that you can't go home anymore.
我没能见到我儿子
I didn't get to see my son.
我没给他钱交学费
I didn't give him money for tuition.
请把学费给他
Please give it to him.
告诉他呆在家里，我的人会把钱给他的
Tell him to be at home, my people will bring him the money.
我会照顾好你儿子
Your son is my concern.
谢谢你
Thank you.
米里奇，我需要你的人手
Mirich, I need some of your men.
好的，我马上就到
All right, I'll be right there.
- 什么? - 米伦，这是什么？
- What? - Milun, what's this?
你在开玩笑吗? 这是什么? ！
Is this a joke? What's this?!
你这个白痴，你可以用它毁掉半个贝尔格莱德
You can destroy half of Belgrade with that, you idiot.
- 用这个? ! - 是的
- With this?! - Yes.
如果你做得好，还会有更多
If you do well, there'll be more.
萨夫科维奇先生，你最近的行为让我很吃惊
Mr. Savkovich, I'm very surprised by your recent actions.
什么行为？
What actions?
你那个疯狂的想法...
That crazy idea of yours...
威胁这个国家最有权势的人
To blackmail one of the most powerful people in the country,
几乎决定了我的命运
almost sealed my destiny.
但就目前情况来看，你的鲁莽行为
But as it stands, with that reckless move of yours,
已经决定了你的命运
you've sealed your destiny.
你的话听起来不太友好，米里奇先生
Your words don't sound very friendly to me, Mr. Mirich.
我们的友谊结束了
Our friendship is over.
我就知道你会这样
I expected something like that from you.
两小时后我要和德国大使共进晚餐
I should have dinner with the German ambassador in two hours.
恐怕他要一个人吃晚餐了
I'm afraid he'll eat alone.
如果我不能及时赶到那里，他会按照我的指示去做
If I don't get there in time, he'll follow my instructions.
国内外所有主要机构
All major institutions, both domestic and foreign,
会收到你多年来的犯罪证据
will have your extensive record that I've been filling for years.
更不用说新时代的特别版了
Not to mention a special edition of the New Age
已经准备好了
which is ready to print
只等你做傻事
just waiting for you to do something stupid.
如果这些还不能让你在监狱里度过余生
If that doesn't put you in Glavnjacha for life,
我的德国朋友会照顾你的
my German friends will take care of you.
你在虚张声势
You're bluffing.
请别再开玩笑了
Let's stop this joke, please.
伟大的事业正在进行，巨大的变化正在到来
Great things are being prepared. Big changes are coming.
如果你想站在胜利一方
If you want to be on the winning side,
就让日瓦科维奇自生自灭吧
leave Zhivkovich to his fate.
我听说你去找托马斯维奇了？
I hear you went after Tomasovich?
- 我会杀了他 - 不要！
- I will liquidate him. - Don't!
他是科罗沙克的人
He is Koroshac's man.
我们还需要科罗沙克先生
And we will need Mr. Koroshac.
你会见到他的
You'll meet with him
并且为他提供服务
and offer him your services.
明白了吗？
Is that clear?
我得走了，我得换衣服去吃晚饭
I have to go, I need to change for dinner.
哦对了，还有件事
And yes, post script...
你最亲近的一个人告发了你
One of your closest people is snitching on you.
再见，米里奇先生
Goodbye, Mr. Mirich.
把这些人送到我告诉你的地方去
Send these people where I told you.
明白吗？
Understood?
好吧，好吧，亚塔汗人..
Well, well, Yataghanians...
你想干什么，混蛋? ！
What do you want, prick?!
- 听着... - 什么？
- Listen... - Yes?
上次我们见面的时候
Last time you and I met,
当时的情况很尴尬
it was a very awkward situation.
我觉得很丢脸
I felt humiliated
而一个被羞辱的人心中充满了仇恨
and a humiliated man is full of hate
仇恨是不健康的..
and hate is not healthy...
它会导致胃灼热
It causes heartburn.
我他妈才不在乎！
I don't give a fuck!
- 这是你的朋友吗? - 是的，是的
- Is this your friend? - Yes, yes.
最好的那个? 你有没有更进一步或者..
The best one? Have you gone further or...
做好你的工作
Just do your job.
我他妈的要杀了你，你这个傻逼！
I'm gonna fucking kill you, you idiot!
不！
No!
你能听到我说话吗？
Can you hear me?
喂？
Hello?
告诉裁缝，从现在开始
Tell the Tailor that from now on,
我要割下所有亚塔汗人的耳朵
I'll cut off the ears of all the Yataghanians.
我们走
Let's go.
无名英雄
U.H.
恭喜你督察
Congratulations, Inspector.
恭喜什么？
For what?
阿森尼耶 · 拉贾奇基遇难
ARSENIYE RAJACHKI KILLED
如果我们没有听从你的指示
If we hadn't listened to your instructions,
就会少一起谋杀案
we would have one less murder.
真的吗？
Oh, really?
什么意思？
What do you mean?
“不要逮捕他，他毕竟是前任局长”
"Don't arrest him, he's a former chief after all."
“他会来投降的”
"He'll come and surrender."
我知道他是怎么投降的了
I see how he surrendered.
他没来是他的不对..
It's not right that he didn't come...
他会因此惹上麻烦的
And he'll be in trouble for that.
但这并不意味着会少一个谋杀案
But it doesn't mean you would have one less murder.
你表现得好像他是你的亲兄弟
You act like he's your blood brother.
我们有证据而你却在保护他！
We have the evidence and you're protecting him!
你有什么，别扯淡了！
What do you have, don't bullshit!
他和拉贾奇基有什么关系？
What has he got to do with Rajachki?
你把两件事放在一起，立刻就指责那个人！
You put two things together and immediately accused the man!
你盲目指责他，但你没有看到
You attacked him, and you don't see
你面前发生了什么！
what's happening in front of you!
- 你看出来了? - 是的
- And you see it, right? - I do.
所以我不能逮捕他？
And that's why I shouldn't arrest him?
好吧，现在你不得不逮捕他，但这解决不了任何问题
Well, now you have to, but that won't solve anything.
不知道我为什么要找你帮忙
Don't know why I asked you for help.
别指手画脚的，你这个傻孩子！
Stop bossing around, you stupid kid!
难道你没有发现有人在给你下套吗？！
Don't you see that someone is setting you up all the time?!
分散你的注意力！
To distract you!
- 为什么? - 因为日尔诺夫，你个白痴！
- From what? - From Zhrnov, you idiot!
日尔诺夫
From Zhrnov.
是一切开始的地方，这就是关键
That's where it all started, that's the key.
好吧
Okay.
你到底要不要带我们去赌场？
Do you want to show us the casino or not?
好吧... 我不在乎
Yeah, right... I don't give a fuck.
我也是这么想的
That's what I thought.
好吧，让你很遗憾，但是幸好
Well, much to your regret, and fortunately for us,
我们年轻的同事组织了后续调查
our young colleague organized your follow-up.
我们不再需要你的帮助了
We won't need your help anymore.
我们走
Let's go.
干得好
Great job.
你说了你该说的
You said what you had to say.
再见了，同志们！
Goodbye, colleagues!
乔科老师
Master Djoko.
穆斯塔法·戈卢比奇，对吗？
And I am Mustapha Golubich, right?
这就是你和那个该死的 IMRO
That's why there will never be anything
永远成不了气候的原因
from you and that fucking IMRO.
因为我知道你是谁？
Because I know who you are?
因为你很蠢，还吹牛
Because you're stupid and brag about it.
你不遵守比你聪明的人
You don't follow the rules of conspiracy,
写的阴谋论的规则
written by someone smarter than you.
你是来教我的还是...
You came here to teach me or...
我们不教像你这样的人，我们杀了他们
We don't teach people like you, we kill them.
谁会杀了我？
And who's gonna kill me?
你在马其顿的手下？
Your men in Macedonia?
我的意思是，我的人变成了你的人
I mean, my men who became yours.
听着...如果我说了算，我会把他们全部干掉
Look... If it's up to me, I'd destroy them all
因为我们摧毁了保加利亚 IMRO
as we destroyed the Bulgarian IMRO.
但这不是我能决定的
But it's not up to me,
你们的人愿意倾听，而且会受到保护
yours have offered to listen and will be protected.
怎么保护？
How protected?
把他们变成共产主义者？
By turning them into communists?
这有什么不好吗？
What's wrong with that?
这对我不好
It's bad for me.
奥地利 维也纳
VIENNA, AUSTRIA
请坐
Have a seat.
发生了什么？
What happened?
拉贾奇基被杀了
Rajachki was killed.
这是怎么回事？
How did it happen?
他给我发电报之后就被杀了
He was killed after he wrote to me
说有些重要的事情需要公之于众
that something important needs to be revealed.
好像有人知道我们在准备什么..
As if someone knows what we are preparing...
这样，你会见到那个混蛋帕维里奇
Here's how we do it. You'll meet with that jerk Pavelich
尽可能多地给他钱
and provide him with money as much as he needs.
越快越好
As soon as possible.
至于其他的，我们再联系
For the rest, we'll be in touch.
那你打算怎么办？
And what are you going to do?
我要去贝尔格莱德
I'm travelling to Belgrade.
他们不能杀死你，怎么能杀死国王呢？
How do they think they can kill the king when they couldn't kill you?
也许万乔 · 米海洛夫能帮到他们
Maybe that shit Vancho Mihailov will help them.
真的吗？
Really?
他们见过吗？
Have they met with him?
即使他们见过，也没告诉我
Even if they have, they didn't tell me anything.
你知道帕维里奇和保加利亚人是谁联系的吗？
Do you know who connects Pavelich with the Bulgarians?
我知道
I do.
通过迪多·克瓦特尼克和安特·戈迪纳
Dido Kvaternik and Ante Godina.
- 戈迪纳? - 是的
- Godina? - Yes.
他们两个也陷害了我
The two of them set me up too.
好吧
Well, well...
当我们掌权时
When we're in power,
如果你听话，你会得到你的马其顿共和国的！
you'll get your fucking Republic of Macedonia if you listen!
告诉我关于的戈迪纳的一切信息
Tell me everything you know about Godina.
干得好，维瑞加
Well done, Veriga.
- 干得好 - 谢谢老大
- Good job. - Thanks, boss.
他们是怎么找到拉贾奇基的..
How did they find Rajachki...
残缺的尸体
So mutilated?
你觉得是谁干的？
Who do you think could have done that?
首先是法官..
First the judge...
然后是维多杰，现在又轮到拉贾奇基..
Then the scoundrel Vidoje and now Rajachki...
有人要杀和我共事的人
Someone is killing my associates.
也许我是最后一个目标？
Maybe I'm the last target?
我不敢相信... 谁敢？
I don't believe it... Who would dare?
我不知道，有很多嫉妒的人
I don't know, there are a lot of envious people.
但如果他是冲着我来的，那他就错了
But he's fucking mistaken if he went after me.
无论如何，我为拉贾奇基感到难过
In any case, I feel sorry for Rajachki,
他是个很好的合作伙伴
he was a good collaborator...
我们一起做了很多工作
We did a lot of work together.
我会很想念他的
I will really miss him.
但话又说回来，谁他妈的在乎他！
But then again, who gives a fuck about him!
那个阳痿的傻逼，我很高兴他最后变成那样
He was a prepotent cunt and I'm glad he ended up like that.
他配不上更好的结局
He didn't deserve better.
把这个拿到储藏室去
Take this to the stockroom.
还有...
And please...
告诉尼娜马上过来
Tell Nina to come right away.
- 是的老大 - 谢谢
- Yes, boss. - Thank you.
你们两个! 过来！
You two! Come here!
贝尔格莱德警察
BELGRADE POLICE
那可不是明智之举！
That wouldn't be smart!
把枪放下
Put the gun down.
我和这件事一点关系也没有
I have nothing to do with it.
有人陷害我
Someone set me up.
迪米特里耶维奇，别做傻事
Dimitriyevich, let's not do anything stupid.
我们只想问你几个问题
We just want to ask you a few questions.
把枪放下
Put the gun down.
求你了
Please.
你知道程序，带他回警局
You know the procedure. We're taking him to Glavnjacha.
米里奇先生！
Mr. Mirich!
你找我？
You called me?
你给我买了我要的白兰地了吗？
Did you get me that cognac I asked for?
是的，如你所愿
Yes, as you wished.
你知道你让我想起了谁吗？
Do you know who you remind me of?
我母亲
My mother.
她有着如此美丽而精致的面部特征
She had such beautiful and delicate facial features.
她拥有那种永恒的美
She had that timeless beauty.
她是一个勤奋而诚实的女人
She was a hardworking and honest woman.
诚实
Honest.
就像你一样
Just like you.
你这么认为？
You think so?
不，我不这么认为
No, I don't.
我当然不这么想
Of course I don't.
你认为我能把我母亲和你这样的妓女相提并论吗？
Do you think I can compare my mother with a whore like you?
你真的这么想吗？
Do you really think that?
- 不... - 我妈妈是个妓女？
- No... - That my mother was a whore?
- 不，我没有... - 不，你有
- No, I didn't... - Yes, you did.
- 快说 - 我没有
- Say it. - I didn't.
快说: “阿里米皮耶，你妈妈是个妓女!”
Just say: "Alimpiye, your mother is a whore!"
来吧，说出来
Come on, say it.
尽管说吧！
Feel free to say it!
我不能这么说
I can't say that.
是的，她是
Well, she was.
她和每个人都上过床，就像你一样
She fucked everyone, just like you.
这条鞭子..
This whip...
让我想起了当我淘气的时候
Reminds me of something my father beat me with
我父亲用来打我的东西
when I was naughty.
过来，把手给我
Come here and give me your hands.
现在
Now.
你的手真柔软
You have such gentle hands.
不像我的母亲，她的手因为在冷水中洗衣服而变得粗糙
Unlike my mother, who had rough hands from washing in cold water.
我一直信任你，我的信任是一份礼物..
I always trusted you, and my trust is a gift...
不是每个人都能得到的，过来
That not everyone can receive. Come here.
过来！
Come here!
把手给我
Give me your hands.
把手给我！
Give me your hands!
我的信任是会消失的，你同意吗？
My trust is something that can be lost, do you agree?
对吧? 把手给我! 把手给我！
Right? Give me the hands! Give me your hands!
诺维奇的事我信任了你，但我不知道为什么
I trusted you about Nowicki, and I don't know why.
但那是因为我有你的弱点
But that's because I have a weakness for you.
把这个姿态当作礼物
Take this gesture as a gift.
最后一次，不会再有了
The last one. There will be no more of them.
你可以走了，谢谢你的白兰地
You can go now. Thanks for the cognac.
二十三..
Twenty-three...
二十四..
Twenty-four...
- 25... 太棒了! 太棒了! - 把钱给我！
- Twenty-five... Yes! Bravo! - Give me the money!
- 干得好! - 你看到了吗? ！
- Great job! - Did you see that?!
- 我们去吃蛋糕吧 - 你真执着
- Let's have a cake. - You're so persistent.
你最终会嫁给我的！
You will eventually marry me!
过来帮忙，别再胡闹了
Come here to help, stop foolin' around.
- 为什么是我? - 还有谁? ！
- Why me? - Who else?!
你要尊重等级制度
You have to respect the hierarchy.
那是什么？
What's that?
报纸... 是拉雷从印刷厂拿来的
Paper... Lale took it from the printing house.
- 叫什么名字? - 新时代
- What's it called? - The New Age.
我可以每周都带来
I can bring it every week.
太好了，按箱给你算钱
Great, you'll get money per box.
越薄越好，这样我们就可以把烟叶包起来
As thin as possible, so that we can wrap the tobacco.
我们会赚钱，我们会做一些正经的生意
We'll make money, we'll do some serious business.
想一想
Think a bit.
和警察说话时要集中精神！
Concentrate when talking to the police!
他是前警察
He's an ex cop.
不存在前妓女和前警察
There are no ex whores and ex cops.
- 拜托! - 去你妈的！
- Oh, come on! - Go fuck yourself!
想想! 他会因此被绞死的
Think! He can be hanged for that.
我告诉过你! 我要刺刀干什么? ！
I told you! What do I need a bayonet for?!
也许是你偷来卖的
Maybe you stole it to sell it.
我不偷东西，我是个诚实的女人
I don't steal, I'm an honest woman.
好吧
Yeah, right.
Okay.
它可能被某个来赌博的人拿走了
It may have been taken by one of those who come to gamble.
试着回忆一下
Try to remember.
你怎么会让这种事发生在拉贾奇基身上？
How did you let this happen to Rajachki?
我的朋友被捕了
My friend is arrested.
我必须设法帮助他
I had to try to help him.
- 你的朋友? ! - 是的
- Your friend?! - Yes.
你不在乎我吗？
And you don't care about me?
你知道我可能是下一个吗？
Do you realize that I might be the next one?
谁杀了他？
Who killed him?
我不确定
I'm not sure about that.
- 你不确定? - 我不确定
- You're not sure? - I'm not.
我不是派你去跟踪他了吗？
Didn't I send you to follow him?
你没有派我去做任何事！
You didn't send me anywhere!
我不是你的走狗！
I'm not one of your lackeys so you can send me everywhere!
注意你的言辞！
Watch your tongue!
你知道你是谁吗? ! 你是个自私的人！
Do you know who you are?! You're a selfish man!
别说了
Stop it.
你假装是一个正直的人
You play a righteous man,
但事实上你是个不能爱任何人的懦夫！
but in fact you're a coward who can't love anyone!
- 住口! - 这就是为什么你是一个人！
- Stop it! - That's why you're alone!
- 你永远都是! - 别说了！
- And you'll always be! - Stop it, now!
你让他们杀了索尼娅，也会让他们杀了我！
You let them kill Sonya and you'll let them kill me!
闭上你的臭嘴！
Shut the fuck up!
别拿你自己和她比，婊子！
Don't compare yourself to her, bitch!
来啊，打我啊！
Come on, hit me!
滚！
Go away!
我不想再见到你！
I don't want to see you again!
你不会再见到我了
You won't.
如果你帮不了我，至少为她报仇吧
If you can't help me, at least avenge her.
做点什么！
Do something!
或者死在这个贫民窟里！
Or die in this slum!
- 有什么要说的吗? - 没有
- Have something to say? - No.
拜托，我了解你
Come on, I know you.
我不喜欢这里，丹尼洛
I don't like it here, Danilo.
自从我们到了以后，一切都变得不对劲了
Ever since we arrived, everything turns out to be wrong.
你想让我们回纽约吗？
Would you like us to go back to New York?
那是最明智的
That would be the smartest.
但那有什么荣誉可言？
But is it the most honourable?
谁在乎荣誉，这个行业没有荣誉
Who cares about honour, it's not in this business.
你还记得..
Do you remember when...
他们把带血的衬衫扔进坟墓，在贝洛帕维奇？
They threw bloody shirts into the grave, in Bjelopavlich?
他们说不把我们也送进坟墓
And they said they wouldn't stop
绝不停手？
until they put us in that grave, too?
- 我记得 - 他们停了吗？
- I remember. - Did they stop?
是的，因为我们把他们放进了坟墓
Yes, because we put them into the grave.
为什么我们比他们更坏？
And why are we worse than them?
我们没有变坏，我们还活着
We're not worse, we're alive.
但你想死在这里，丹尼洛
But you want to die here, Danilo.
不是吗？
Don't you?
扎玛罗，他们杀了我的维利科
Zhmaro, they killed my Velyko.
我可以放下任何事，但我不能放不下我的兄弟
I could forgive him everything, but I can't forgive my brother.
好吧，我们留下
Okay, we'll stay.
把他们都杀光
To kill 'em all.
约旦！
Yordan!
你怎么了? 感冒了吗？
What happened to you? Did you catch a cold?
不，你看他牙疼
No, you see he has a toothache.
哦，别逗了，黑山人
Oh, just fuck with me, Montenegrins.
迪米特里耶维奇先生，你要咖啡还是要酒？
Mr. Dimitriyevich, would you like a coffee or some alcohol?
不要打断程序
Don't interrupt the procedure.
你有证据吗？
Do you have evidence for this?
探长，我可以告诉他吗？
Inspector, may I tell him?
叫日沃因过来
Call Zhivoyin.
我们有证人
We have witnesses.
我们有目击证人看到你离开犯罪现场
We have witnesses who saw you leave the crime scene.
什么证人？
What witnesses?
证人看到我杀人了吗？
Did they see me kill, too?
- 那法官呢? - 他怎么了？
- And the judge? - What about him?
他在你的赌场赌博
He gambled at your place.
那又怎样? 一半的政府人员都在那儿赌博
So? Half the government gambled there.
是的，但是你和他有冲突
Yes, but you had a conflict with him.
就算有... 谁没有呢？
Even if I had... Who didn't?
你以为只有我一个跟他又冲突吗？
You think I was the only one?
就是他，愿蛇把他的眼睛挖出来！
That's him, may the snake take his eyes out!
别紧张，拉杰科
Easy, Rajko.
- 他是谁? - 那个吸血鬼
- Who "him"? - The vampire.
那个已经死了的人！
The one whose name is dead!
日沃因! 这是怎么回事? ！
Zhivoyin! What's this?!
- 警长先生...-肃静！
- Mr. chief... - Silence!
是这个人杀了矿工巴雅克塔维奇吗？
Did this man kill the miner Baryaktarevich?
就是他
He did.
这个人杀了他，我，你... 他会杀了所有人！
He killed him, me, you... He'll kill all of us!
把他带走！
Take him away!
迪米特里耶维奇先生..
Mr. Dimitriyevich...
我以多重谋杀罪逮捕你
I'm arresting you for multiple premeditated murders.
你要逮捕谁，混蛋? ！
Whom are you arresting, motherfucker?!
我? 我雇你来的！
Me? I hired you here!
白痴! 我把你送到瑞士，这样他们就不会停你的职！
Idiot! I sent you to Switzerland so they wouldn't suspend you!
去你妈的！
Go fuck yourself!
那个修道士把这里烧得很惨
Well, the Monk burned you well.
我们不能再这样下去了
We can't do this anymore.
我要弄死他！
I'm gonna fuck him to death!
简单! 他很幸运
Easy! He was lucky.
他在等你发疯
He's waiting for you to go crazy.
完全迷失自我
To completely lose it.
他想引诱你
He wants to lure you.
如果你现在去找他你就完蛋了
If you go after him now, you'll be fucked up,
你也会让我惹上麻烦的
and you'll get me in shit, too.
- 我该怎么办? - 冷静点
- What should I do? - Calm down.
带手下去马其顿找基拉
Take the boys to Kyro's in Macedonia.
等我完成一些工作，然后我会带更多的人来
Wait for me to finish some work, then I'll bring more people.
然后我们一起杀了他
Then we'll kill him together,
把他吊在市中心
and hang him by the balls in the middle of the city.
去马其顿就相当于把贫民窟拱手让给他
To go to Macedonia and leave the Yataghan slum to him...
没有保护？
Unprotected?
你真的有东西要留在这..
And you really have something to leave...
得了吧！
Come on!
如果他拆了这个贫民窟
If he demolishes this slum,
等我们回来，我们会造一个更好的
we'll make a nicer and better one when we get back.
米兰！
Milan!
让我们做些正事吧
Let's do some work.
上帝保佑你！
God bless you!
你好！
Hello!
这真的很不舒服，但你知道规则
This is really uncomfortable but you know the rules.
我保证我们会加快调查
I promise we will speed up the investigation.
等等！
Wait!
你以经营非法赌场的罪名逮捕我？
You arrested me for running an illegal casino?
不，是以多重谋杀罪逮捕你
No, but on suspicion you committed multiple premeditated murders.
你有什么具体的证据？
What concrete evidence do you have for your claim?
你带来了那个疯子为了不让自己内疚
You brought that lunatic who would accuse his mother
甚至可以指控他母亲！
just to save himself from his guilt!
有人看见我在房子前面，那又怎样? ！
Someone saw me in front of the house, so what?!
你们什么都没有！
You have nothing!
恐怕是的
I'm afraid we have.
迪米特里耶维奇先生！
Mr. Dimitriyevich!
这是你的刺刀吗？
Is this your bayonet?
是的，有人从我的赌场偷走的
Yes, they stole it from my casino.
维多杰先生和他的妻子索尼娅就是被它杀死的
Mr. Vidoje and his wife Sonya were killed with it.
在犯罪现场附近发现的
It was found near the crime scene.
经证实，刺刀上的指纹是你的
It's been confirmed that the prints on the bayonet are yours.
- 有人陷害我 - 谁？
- They set me up. - Who?
我可以打个电话吗？
Can I make a phone call?
- 儿子! - 我不是你儿子
- Son! - It's not Strahinja.
他现在还活着
He's alive. For now.
如果你想让他活命的话，你知道该怎么做
If you want him to stay that way, you know what to do.
我有罪
I'm guilty.
我是凶手
I'm the killer.
哦，亲爱的..
Oh, my dear...
拉贾奇基是我们公司的重要合作伙伴
Rajachki was a significant partner of our company.
非常重要的一个
A significant one.
他死后，我们将陷入严重的麻烦
After his death, we'll get into serious trouble.
更不用说
Not to mention,
他也是你丈夫生意上的合伙人
he was a partner in your husband's business as well.
而这个生意是我们的负担
And that business is a burden on our backs.
我们很快就会给克劳斯一个答复
We will reveal that thing with Klaus soon.
他还是没付钱给我们
He still hasn't paid us anything.
一分钱都没付
Nothing.
玛雅夫人
Mrs. Maya.
- 萨夫科维奇先生 - 让他进来
- Mr. Savkovich. - Let him in.
请进，先生
Come in, sir.
- 萨夫科维奇先生! - 你好，帕帕哈吉先生
- Mr. Savkovich! - Hello, Mr. Papahagi.
- 请坐 - 非常感谢
- Have a seat. - Thank you very much.
有何贵干，萨夫科维奇先生？
How can we help you, Mr. Savkovich?
现在我们亲爱的兄弟走了
Now that our beloved brother is gone,
我们要给他应得的死后荣誉
it remains for us to pay him the posthumous honour he deserves.
帕皮和我会处理的
Papi and I will take care of that.
委员会指定我来处理这件事
The council appointed me to take care of it.
我不知道为什么，但我马上就来告诉你
I don't know why, but I came right away to tell you.
谢谢你
Thank you.
我可能应该把这当成一个信息..
I should probably take that as a message...
你觉得呢，帕皮？
What do you think, Papi?
也许他们只是认为这样的葬礼是男人的工作
Maybe they just think that such funerals are a man's job.
也许他们也是这么想的
Maybe they think the same about the Order Master position.
玛雅！
Maya!
我相信没有人会想到这样的事情
I'm sure no one thinks of such a thing.
如果你愿意，我可以再打电话给总部
If you want, I can call the headquarters again.
不，不必了...
No, please...
我不想让你觉得我是在背着你做事
I wouldn't want you to think I'm doing something on my own.
当然不是，照我说的做就是了
Of course not. Just do as you are told.
谢谢，萨夫科维奇先生
Thanks, Mr. Savkovich.
再见
Goodbye.
帕皮
Papi!
当你开始检查拉贾奇基的文件时
When you start checking Rajachki's papers,
注意他们怎么合作的，有多大金额，合作对象是...
pay attention to how and how much he cooperated with...
- 克劳斯! - 那个也是
- Klaus! - That, too.
但主要还是和奥布拉德·萨夫科维奇
But primarily, with Obrad Savkovich.
越快越好
As soon as possible.
朱巴？
Ljuba?
朱巴！
Ljuba!
谢谢
Thanks.
我想和他谈谈
I want to talk to him.
就算我想把你弄进去，你也知道这是严重的冒犯
Even if I wanted to get you inside, you know it'd be a serious offence.
你已经不在警局工作了
You have nothing to do there.
你怎么这么蠢？
How come you're so stupid?
迪米特里耶维奇和谋杀案有什么关系？
What has Dimitriyevich got to do with the murders?
你看不出有人陷害他吗？
You can't see someone set him up?
为什么会有人陷害他？
Why would anyone set him up?
我不知道
I don't know.
也许是因为反对拆除那个贫民窟的签名
Maybe because of the signatures against the demolition of that slum.
那些签名并不是反对拆迁
Those signatures weren't against the demolition,
而是支持拆除贫民窟的签名
the signatures were in favour to demolish the Yataghan slum.
他和法官想要栽赃
He and the judge wanted to plant it.
天啊
Oh, man,
你难道看不出他和谋杀案没有关系吗？
don't you realize he has nothing to do with the murders?
塔尼，他已经认罪了！
Tane, he has admitted the guilt!
你知道我很感激你，无论是作为一个人还是作为一个警察
You know that I appreciate you both as a man and as a policeman.
你心烦意乱，你会发疯的
You're upset, you'll go crazy.
你失去理智了
You're losing it.
- 你说什么? ! - 振作起来！
- What did you say?! - Get yourself together!
让我振作起来? ！
To get myself together?!
你想让我揍你吗？
You want me to beat the shit out of you?
来吧
Go ahead.
嘿，嘿，嘿! 放松！
Hey, hey, hey! Easy!
- 冷静点! - 完全搞错了，你个白痴！
- Easy! - This is so fucked up, idiot!
滚一边去！
Go away!
这一切都和阿皮斯有关
This is related to Apis.
还有黑手党
And the Black Hand.
跟迪米特里耶维奇半毛钱关系都没有
Not to Dimitriyevich.
嘿！
Hey!
塔尼只是在保护他的朋友
Tane is just protecting his friend.
他没有恶意
He didn't mean anything bad.
你好
Hello.
- 朱巴! - 失陪了
- Ljuba! - Excuse me.
你看见塔尼了吗？
Have you seen Tane?
斯坦科，塔尼是我的老上司
Stanko, Tane was my superior.
他带我入行..
He brought me to the service...
我明白
I understand that.
他想要什么？
What did he want?
他想知道巴雅克塔维奇和法官
He wanted to know whether Baryaktarevich and the judge
是不是萨洛尼卡审判的参与者
were participants in the Thessaloniki process.
当阿皮斯和他的军官们企图刺杀国王
When Apis and the officers were accused of high treason
被指控叛国...
for attempting to assassinate His Royal Highness...
我知道萨洛尼卡审判
I know what the Thessaloniki process is.
我不明白这和这个有什么关系
I don't understand what it has to do with this.
巴雅克塔维奇、法官、维多耶
Baryaktarevich, the judge, Vidoje...
每个人都是其中一份子，明白吗? 每个人
Everyone was part of it. Understand? Everyone.
都在文件里了，我给你看看！
I have it all in the documents. Let me show you!
都在这儿了
Here. It's all there.
加快速度，给我！
Speed it up! Gezim, give me that!
- 你在干什么? - 把所有东西都放那儿！
- What are you doing? - Just put everything there!
- 快点，快点! - 不行！
- Come on, come on! - No way!
来吧，格齐姆，所有的东西！
Come on, Gezim, everything!
这不可能！
It's not possible!
把所有能装下的东西都放进去! 快点！
Put everything that can fit! Come on!
小钢炮！
Diesel!
快点，放开那个婊子！
Come on, get off that whore!
快点，我们在等你！
Come on, we're waiting for you!
- 干什么? - 赞内，等等
- What do you want, huh?! - Tzane, wait.
你答应过我的
You gave me a word.
赞内! 有人看见我儿子了吗？
Tzane! Has anyone seen my son?
放我出去！
Let me out!
袜子、毛衣、烤鸡...
Socks, sweater, roasted chicken...
好的，妈妈
Okay, Mum.
- 面包...还有钱! - 谢谢妈妈
- Bread... Take the money! - Thanks, Mum.